Amanda Steele Show.
Fulton County District Attorney Fannie Willis.
Her decision-making acumen has been called into question.
So she hired a man named Nathan Wade as an outside consultant
to work as a special prosecutor on the election subversion case against Donald Trump.
The problem, y'all, apparently this hiring happened while they was having
a possible extramarital affair.
They was going to make sure to find anything.
Like, have we not watched Scandal when Olivia's father, Papa Pope,
made it abundantly clear that we got to work twice as hard and be twice as perfect?
Did we not watch that episode together as a family?
Y'all, we not in a place where we are equal.
So we still got to operate in this way.
And I don't know what this man could have said to her to make her say,
let me put him on the team.
So I need to give y'all some ABC options.
And I want you to call me and tell me what you think it is.
Is it A?
Did Nathan Wade say to Fannie, if you don't hire me,
I'm a snitch on this little thing we got going on.
Could it have been B to keep getting this thing?
You got to put me on the team.
Or could it have been C?
Can you be my Coretta so we can get major together?
This is what I want to know.
A, B, or C.
Which one do you think it was?
We are, we are.